<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:padding="12dp"
    android:background="#f2f9f2"
    tools:context="com.example.sufian.livelocal.AboutFragment">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">
    </ScrollView>
    <TextView
        android:padding="15dp"
        android:background="@drawable/black"
        android:id="@+id/label"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:gravity="left"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        android:textSize="15dp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:textColor="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
        android:text="The Live Local app is designed for users that are ready to discover CT-Grown goods and experience local agriculture. The Live Local app lets users browse upcoming events to find a fun family activity or weekend getaway, while the Seasons Top Ten highlights creative and fun things to do during every season. The Trails section invites users to explore artisan foods in Connecticut, such as cheese, beer, or wine. Users may take a pledge to spend 10 percent of their food and gardening dollars on locally grown products, and then use the app to track how well they are doing meeting that commitment, and then share their progress with friends on Facebook. Finally, the app seeks to build an online community of local food and farm enthusiasts through the Live Local group on Facebook, where users post pictures from their agriculture adventures.\n\n The Live Local app is a tool of the CT 10% Campaign, a public education program of UConn Extension, coordinated in partnership with CitySeed and its buyctgrown program."
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true" />



</RelativeLayout>


